surgedirect.com 2012-09-19

# Surge Direct

Surge Direct Privacy Policy

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.  When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or social security number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

1)  To personalize your experience: Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.

2)  To improve our website: We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

3)  To improve customer service: Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

4)  To process transactions:  Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

5)  To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

6)  To send periodic emails:  The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

How do we protect your information?  

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.  We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.  After a transaction, your private information such as credit cards and financials will not be stored on our servers.

Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers’ hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.  

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Third party links:  Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance:

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.  As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at any time by logging into their account and going to the 'Profile' page.

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance:

Collecting personal information from children under the age of 18 (&quot;minor children&quot;) through the Services or the Blog is prohibited. No Content should be directed toward minor children. Minor children are not eligible to use the site, and we ask that they do not submit any personal information to us.

Online Privacy Policy Only:  This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Terms and Conditions:  Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.surgedirect.com/terms_service.php

Your Consent:  By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy:  If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
